var init = {
    'questions': [{
        'question': 'A microbial fuel cell is a device that converts chemical energy to electrical energy by the catalytic reaction of ________ ?',
        'answers': ['Bacteria', 'Microorganism', 'Biology', 'Fungus'],
        'correctAnswer': 1
    },{
        'question': 'The idea of using microbial cells in an attempt to produce ________ was first conceived at the turn of the nineteenth century.',
        'answers': ['Electric charge', 'Electricity', 'Electromagnetism', 'Magnetism'],
        'correctAnswer': 2
	},{
        'question': 'A professor of botany at the University of Durham, Potter managed to generate electricity from ________, however the work was not to receive any major coverage.',
        'answers': ['Pathogenic bacteria', 'Pseudomonas aeruginosa', 'Escherichia coli', 'Helicobacter pylori'],
        'correctAnswer': 3
    },{
        'question': 'MFCs could be installed to ________ treatment plants.',
        'answers': ['Freshwater environmental quality parameters', 'Wastewater', 'Water pollution', 'Water quality'],
        'correctAnswer': 2
	},{
        'question': 'In the anode compartment, fuel is oxidized by microorganisms, generating ________ and protons.',
        'answers': ['Positron', 'Photon', 'Atom', 'Electron'],
        'correctAnswer': 4
	},{
        'question': 'A typical microbial fuel cell consists of ________ and cathode compartments separated by a cation specific membrane.',
        'answers': ['Rechargeable battery', 'Galvanic cell', 'Battery (electricity)', 'Anode'],
        'correctAnswer': 4
	},{
        'question': 'Bacteria in mediator-less MFCs typically have electrochemically-active redox ________ such as cytochromes on their outer membrane that can transfer electrons to external materials.',
        'answers': ['Enzyme inhibitor', 'Cofactor (biochemistry)', 'Protein', 'Enzyme'],
        'correctAnswer': 3
	},{
        'question': 'A microbial fuel cell (MFC) or biological fuel cell is a bio-________ system that drives a current by mimicking bacterial interactions found in nature.',
        'answers': ['Chlorine', 'Chemistry', 'Electrochemistry', 'Analytical chemistry'],
        'correctAnswer': 2
	},{
        'question': 'In fact, it was recently published that a ________ curve was obtained between the anodic potential and the power output of an acetate driven microbial fuel cell.',
        'answers': ['Protein', 'Enzyme kinetics', 'Michaelis–Menten kinetics', 'Enzyme'],
        'correctAnswer': 3
	},{
        'question': 'In general, there are two types of microbial ________, mediator and mediator-less microbial fuel cells.',
        'answers': ['Fuel cell', 'Zinc-air battery', 'Flow battery', 'Lead-acid battery'],
        'correctAnswer': 1
	}, ],
    'resultComments': {
        perfect: '',
        excellent: '',
        good: '',
        average: '',
        bad: '',
        poor: '',
        worst: ''
    }

};